Contact

225 Garðabær, Iceland (+354) 866-1321 (Mobile) jonnxor@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/jonnxor (LinkedIn) www.jonnxor.is/ (Personal)

Top Skills

Next.js

React.js

TypeScript

Languages

Icelandic (Native or Bilingual) English (Professional Working)

Jón Agnar Stefánsson

Senior Frontend Web Developer Iceland

Summary

Web Developer with one decade's worth of experience in popular web technologies and methodologies.

Worked on multiple projects in a wide variety of web frameworks, with a strong focus on project architecture, maintainability, readability, performance optimizations, and strict adherence to best practices.

I have had a passion for technology since a young age and am always interested in ways to improve my skills and knowledge through continuous learning and knowledge-sharing opportunities.

Additionally, other interests include art, culture, language, history, mythology, philosophy, and more.

Experience

Advania Ísland Web Developer May 2016 - April 2024 (8 years) Reykjavík, Iceland

Web & App development, maintenance and service for Advania Iceland.

Reykjavik University Teaching Assistant 2016 - 2016 (less than a year) Reykjavík, Iceland

Teaching web development for Reykjavík University.

Skeljungur Attendant 2015 - 2015 (less than a year)

Reykjavík, Capital Region, Iceland

Gas Station Attendant

Outcome Technician 2012 - 2014 (2 years) Reykjavík, Iceland

IT, Customer Support and Marketing Email Development.

Education

Reykjavik University

Bachelor of Science - BS, Computer Science · (2013 - 2016)

Technical College of Iceland
Associate's degree, Computer Science · (2009 - 2013)